Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Comparative Literature, Honors Theses SC4-3433
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Comparative Literature, honors theses
1996-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Comparative Literature
SC4-3433
1.25 Linear Feet (13 volumes in 3 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Comparative Literature.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Comparative Literature.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Student papers.; Comparative literature -- Study and teaching.; Stanford University. Department of Comparative Literature
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Antognini, Albertina, The literary practice of philosophy: the phenomenology of Palomar., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Haslanger, Andrea, The physical mind and the thinking world: the poetry of Wallace Stevens., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Jernigan, Adam, Nabokov's naughty narrators: panoptic structures of narrative authority in Nabokov's American novels., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Lash, Cristina, Extra-realism in the contemporary slave narratives of Toni Morrison and Manual Zapata Olivella., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Lindsey, Ursula, In search of lost Paris: the city in literature: space, time, memory and nostalgia., undated (Box 1)
  - Schachter, Allison, Inscriptions of the errant past: memories through language, memorials of the Holocaust., 1996 (Box 1)
  - Milburn, Colin, Bleeding texts and monstrous authors: theorizing horror., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Sheehan, Rebecca and Katherine Anya Smucker Lemons, Imperative to critique: defamiliarizing the Silicon Valley., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, J. Bradford, An aristocracy of readers: canon formation in Joris-Karl Huysmans' A rebours., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Powell, Jessica, El buscapiés del pensamiento: Oliverio Girondo y Ramón Gómez de la Serna., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Lewis-Kraus, Gideon, Uncalled-for to this day: psychoanalysis and pragmatism in the service of self and culture., 2002 (Box 2)
  - Ewald, Marie, Representing the south: reflections on Carlo Levi and Danilo Dolci., 2000 (Box 2)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Sun, Vicki, "What is a minor literature? The (re) writing of a more gender-equal Islam by three Muslin women living and writing in the west", 2011 (Box 1)